export const QuizData = [
    {
        question : 'What is React.js primarily used for ?',
        options : [ "Data storage", "Styling", "User interface development", "Server-side scripting"],
        answer : 3
    },
    {
        question : 'Which of the following is NOT a built-in API in Node.js?',
        options : [ "EventEmitter", "Buffer", "Console", "Navigator"],
        answer : 4
    },
    {
        question : 'Which of the following is used to create a new React element ?',
        options : [ "createElement()", "createNode()", "createComponent()", "newElement()"],
        answer : 1
    },
    {
        question : 'In Node.js, which object represents the global scope?',
        options : [ "global", "window", "document", "process"],
        answer : 1
    },
    {
        question : 'Which lifecycle method is called after a components output has been rendered to the DOM?',
        options : [ "componentDidMount", "componentDidUpdate", "componentWillMount", "componentWillUnmount"],
        answer : 2
    },
    {
        question : 'Which React Hook is used to manage state in functional components?',
        options : [ "useState", "useEffect", "useReducer", "useContext"],
        answer : 1
    },
    {
        question : 'In JSX, which syntax is used to embed JavaScript expressions?',
        options : [ "{% ... %}", "{{ ... }}", "${ ... }", "{...}"],
        answer : 3
    },
    {
        question : 'Which of the following is not a core module in Node.js?',
        options : [ "fs (File System)", "http (Hypertext Transfer Protocol)", "req (Request)", "os (Operating System)"],
        answer : 3
    },
    {
        question : 'In Node.js, which module is used for reading and writing files?',
        options : [ "url", "querystring", "fs (File System)", "http"],
        answer : 3
    },
    {
        question : 'What is the default package manager that comes with Node.js?',
        options : [ "Yarn", "NPM (Node Package Manager)", "Pip", "Composer"],
        answer : 2
    }
]